

Ammar Elsheikh

PROFILE

I am currently in my 4th year of computer science studies, majoring in software Engineering at University Malaysia Pahang. I have managed projects in several programing languages such as C, C++, and Java, and have undertaken both web and mobile based applications projects.

With my engineering coursework and projects experience, my innovative mindset and affinity for problem solving, and my history of successful team projects, I believe I am a strong candidate for this role.

CONTACT



elsheikh.ammar@gmail.com



+601135609316



Pahang, Malaysia



https://fitday-8341c.web.app/

HOBBIES



Photography







EDUCATION

University Malaysia Pahang Bachelor of Computer Science (Software **Engineering) With Honors** 2016-2021

Nasser Secondary School High School Certificate 2011-2014

EXPERIENCE

C Language Project Shopping System 2017-2018

HTML, PHP, CSS and JAVASCRIPT **Project**

Car Rental System 2018-2019

EX-CO of Academic Egyptian Students in University Malaysia Pahang **Responsible for 45 Egyptian Students** 2019-2020

JAVASCRIPT, JAVATYPE, HTML and **CSS FINAL YEAR PROJECT** Fitness Mobile and Web based

2020-2021

TOP SKILLS

Web Application Problem Solving C C++ Front-End Development Level 1 TRIZ Practitioner Programing Language Programing Language **Critical Thinking TeamWork** HTML5 **PHP** Thinking out of the box Personal Skills **Programing Language** Programing Language **Time Management SDLC JAVA MYSQL** Software Development **Projects Management** Database **Programing Language** Life Cycle **JAVASCRIPT Arabic English PHOTOSHOP** Writing, Speaking and Writing, Speaking and **Programing Language** Photos Editing and 3D Reading Reading Logos

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES